pcsupportdock.com 2017-11-21

# Systweak Software – Privacy Policy

You can visit our website, read products description and other materials, and check on offerings without giving us any personally identifiable information. Since we provide our customers and newsletter subscribers with the most efficient and enhanced personalized service; we may request information about you under occasional circumstances. For your convenience and to serve you better, a customer account includes all the collected personal information we may have, however, you can update or correct your contact information or change your preferences about receiving newsletter and other information from us.

We collect personally identifiable information; such as name, mailing address and e-mail address when you register to one of our products or place an order (see the section below for more information on placing order). Website visitors may register to receive our newsletter by submitting their name and e-mail address.

####  Placing Orders

If you wish to place an order for our products, you can generally enter the requisite details. In addition to the customary information that may be required to fill your order (full name, address, phone number, ship-to name and address etc.), collection of additional information such as your credit card number and credit card expiration date, is dependent on option of payment as we offer online and offline subscribers additional options such as check, money order and credit card order by fax or phone.

####  Use of Programs

In connection with the installation and use of Systweak Software applications we may collect certain information concerning the use of application or the services, including certain personal data and information about your PC. This may include, information about your installed software and hardware, your IP address, your operating system, about your version of installed Systweak Software's application including its product key, and about the use of individual functions of that Systweak Software's application including the relevant times. Some applications are dependant on use of WebServices for their functioning and they do send such relevant data with each use.

Purpose of Data Collection

Applications and Services can use the aforementioned information to send product recommendations, product updates and important customer service notifications directly to your computer. Furthermore, the data is used for the purposes of product and market analysis which enables us to improve individual products and the range of products and services.

Sharing of Data with Third Party

The aforementioned data may be shared with third party vendors and partners and it will be governed by their privacy policy, which will be provided to you when you accept any offer by them.

Consent for the Collection, Storage, Use and Distribution of the Data You hereby agree to the collection and use of the such information or data by Systweak Software.
